理查・基尔
戴安・莲恩
奥立佛・马丁内兹
《出轨》
外头风好大
Pretty windy out.
千万别是在打暴力电玩 当然不是，妈
- That better not be the violent one. - It's not, Mom.
爸，看我做的
Dad, look what I can do.
我练好久了
I've been practicing.
太出色了，小子 酷!
- Spectacular, kiddo. - Cool.
你衣服穿反了
You're inside out.
我知道 对你不管用吧？
I knew that. Doesn't work for you?
不敢相信你竟然教他那样
I can't believe you taught him that.
我没有，是他自己学的
I didn't. He did it on his own.
查理，你刷牙了没？ 刷了
- Charlie, did you brush your teeth? - Yes.
查理! 我刷过了啦
- Charlie. - I brushed them.
你来看一下，康妮 我们走，我说认真的
- Look at this, Con. - Let's go. I'm serious.
你快把我给逼疯了，妈
You're driving me bonkers, Mom.
还记得你说别买全谷股票吗？
Remember when you said no to buying Omnidell?
记得那时价钱多少吗？ 一股50元
- Remember what the price was? - One fifty.
很接近，是61元
Close. Sixty-one.
我自己来，妈 不，我帮你
- I'll do it, Mom. - No, I'll do it.
你知道现在行情多少了吗？
You know what it's going for now?
说"一"! 一...
- Say "E. " - E.
猜猜看，康妮 爱德华，我不知道，好吗？
- Guess, Con. - Edward, I don't know, all right?
现在漱口吧! 涨到74元了
- Now rinse. - Seventy-four.
真的漱口. 顺便尿个尿
Really rinse. And pee.
74元! 早该买下来，可恶!
Seventy-four. Should have bought it. Shit.
那就买一点嘛! 太迟了，康丝，太迟了
- So buy some. - Too late, Con. Too late.
把盖子掀起来，甜心
Lift the seat, honey.
别忘了放下马桶盖
Don't forget to put it down.
等你尿完的时候
When you finish.
你真的得带这么多东西吗？
- Do you really need all that stuff? - Mom, no one wears these dorky hats.
妈，没有人会戴这种唐老鸭帽啦!
你戴又不表示你是唐老鸭
- You do and you're not a dork. - How do I look?
我看来如何？
很帅
Very handsome.
我爱 好了，快点，要走了
Love you. Okay, come on, let's go.
快点
Come on.
你不应该出门的
You shouldn't go in.
我有些东西要在拍卖会上卖 而且他生日就快到了
I have stuff to do for the auction. And there's a birthday soon.
我要拉特里尔・斯普雷威尔球衣，妈 别忘了
Latrell Sprewell jersey, Mom. Don't forget.
他是扬基队的，对吧？ 妈，你快把我给逼疯了
- He's on the Yankees, right? - Mom, you're driving me bonkers.
你快把他给逼疯了
You're driving him bonkers.
天啊!
Jesus.
出租车! 可恶!
Taxi! Shit.
出租车!
Taxi!
真对不起
I'm so sorry.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我来帮捡东西
I'll get your things.
出租车! 出租车!
Taxi! Taxi!
我的书
My books.
你能帮我拦辆出租车吗？ 好的
- Could you help me get a taxi? - Okay.
我会顾好你的书 谢谢
- I'll watch your books. - Thanks.
惨的连出租车都叫不到 都怪这阵可怕的风
- Bad day for taxis. - It's this horrible wind.
对，你像颗子弹被击倒了!
Yeah, you shot down there like a bullet!
如果你挥动一下手臂 现在早就在家了
If you flapped your arms, you'd be home now.
下回我会记住的
I'll remember that next time.
情况不太妙 我知道
- That's not good. - I know.
听着，我就住在楼上，有花盆那间
Listen, that's me up there. The flowerpot.
我帮你贴个绷带，好吗？
I'll get you a Band-Aid, okay?
抓紧一点，别被吹跑了
Hold onto something. Don't blow away.
还是你要上来清洗一下？
Or you can come on up and clean it off, no?
来吧!
Come on.
我又不是什么连环杀手，我发誓
I'm not an ax murderer. I promise.
可恶!
Shit.
死电梯!
Fucking elevator.
再爬一层就到了
One more.
抱歉这里乱的很 你是个作家？
- Pardon the mess. - Are you a writer?
我是个书商
I'm a book dealer.
浴室就在那里，在左手边
Bathroom's right down there, on the left.
去啊! 里面有个医药柜
Go ahead. There's a medicine cabinet.
你可以偷瞄一下我的药方
You can sneak a peek at my prescriptions.
哈？
Hello?
我替你泡了点茶 谢谢!
- I made you some tea. - Thank you.
你练拳击？ 年轻时候有在练
- Do you box? - I used to, when I was young.
这地方真神奇
This is an amazing place.
没错，但这房子不是我的 不是？
- Yeah, but it's not mine. - No?
屋主是我朋友，他是雕刻家 现在人去了巴黎
The owner is a friend, a sculptor. He's in Paris.
真是酷! 我们可以住在这里，我和我的书
That's cool. We can stay here, me and my books.
可以借个电话吗？ 我得打个电话回家
Can I use your phone? I have to call home.
当然可以! 电话就在你后面
Sure, there's a phone just behind you.
谢谢
Thank you.
葛萝莉亚？ 嗨，是我
Gloria? Hi, it's me.
好，很好. 查理怎样？
Good, good. How's Charlie?
嗨，甜心! 今天在学校过的如何？
Hi, honey. How was your day at school?
真的？ 什么部份最精彩呢？
Yeah? What was the best part?
你猜怎着？ 你相信吗？ 妈咪错过了班车
Guess what? Can you believe it? Mommy missed her train.
冰块
Ice.
约一个小时
About an hour.
你该去做功课了
You should start your homework.
我保证见了面会一五一十地告诉你 我爱你，再见!
I promise to tell you all about it when I see you. I love you. Bye.
是我儿子查理 现在8岁，下周就9岁了
That was my son, Charlie. He's 8. He'll be 9 next week.
我叫保罗・马提尔，我七月份就满28岁了
I'm Paul Martel. I'll be 28 in July.
我叫康丝坦斯，我迟到了，我该走了
I'm Constance. And I'm late. I have to go.
你走之前，拿本书去看吧!
Before you go, take a book.
不，我不行
No. I couldn't.
当然可以，当作纪念品
Sure you can. A souvenir.
走到那边. 你知道，跟之前一样
Go down there. You know, like before.
好吧
Okay.
继续走. 停!
Keep going. Stop.
现在找右边
Now right.
不对，右边
No, right.
好的，从上面数下来第二层书架...
Okay, now the second shelf from the top. . .
...左边数来第四本
. . .take the fourth one from the left.
拿了吗？
Got it?
拿了! 打开第23页
- Think so. - Open to page 23.
品酒: 永恒的人生
Drink wine, this is life eternal
酒，让你回复青春
This, all that youth will give to you
是美酒、玫瑰，把酒狂欢的季节
It is the season for wine, roses And drunken friends
要实时行乐
Be happy for this moment
此刻便是你的人生
This moment is your life
我得走了，谢谢
I have to go. Thank you.
你知道怎么出去吧？ 但愿如此
- Can you find your way out? - I hope so.
那是我的卧房
That's my bedroom.
很高兴遇见你，康丝坦斯
It was nice meeting you, Constance.
如果你需要别的书或医疗就过来这里
Come back if you need more books or medical attention.
嗨，葛萝莉亚
Hey, Glo.
电视该关掉了，是吧？ 我正要关掉
- That wouldn't be the TV on, would it? - I was just turning it off.
想必如此
Sure you were.
风把我吹倒了 真的？
- The wind knocked me down. - Yeah?
你没事吧？ 要不要给医生看一下？
You all right? You need anything?
哇! 你和别人打架了吗？ 不，只是跌倒而已
- Gross. Were you in a fight? - No, just fell over.
痛不痛？ 有一点
- Does it hurt? - Little bit.
酷! 你去哪里？
- Cool! - Where are you going?
去拿相机! 试试这个
- To get the camera! - Try this.
你拿相机要做什么？ 交学校作业用. 我们弄的血腥一点
- Why do you need the camera? - It's for school. We're doing blood.
好的，现在装成真的很痛的样子
Okay, now look like it really hurts.
准备好没？ 好了
- Ready? - Yeah.
这一定很棒!
This will be great.
风把她吹倒，害的她流血了
The wind blew her down. She bled and everything.
每个人的帽子都被吹跑了 好个战地摄影师. 你没事吧？
- Everybody's hats blew off. - Quite the war photographer. You okay?
是的，风把我像个老太婆似的吹倒
Yeah. It took me down like an old lady.
真是丢脸! 爸! 来看看照片
- It was humiliating. - Dad, look at the pictures.
至少我们有了证据 可以告谁吗？
At least we got the evidence. Anyone we can sue?
不能，有一个好心人帮忙我
No. There was this nice guy who helped me.
就像这样，爸 是龙卷风
It was like this, Dad. It was a twister.
爸，你看，就像这样
Dad, look. It was like this.
哇! 是龙卷风
- Wow. - It's a tornado.
他住在那儿附近. 他拿绷带给我还帮我叫了部出租车
He lived around there. He got me some Band-Aids and put me in a taxi.
他长的帅吗？
Was he good-looking?
我觉得不舒服
I feel sick.
你作业写了没？ 还没，我不知道怎么写
- You do your homework? - I can't. I don't know how to do it.
快点，我来帮你 然后你再来帮我
Come on, I'll help you. Then you can help me with mine.
知道他的名字吗？
Did you get his name, this guy?
我们可以送瓶酒给他
We could send him a bottle of wine.
便宜点的
Cheap wine.
康妮，站在那里别动 等一下
Con, stand there a second. Wait a minute.
站在那里一下 我正想办法搞清楚这台....
Stay there a second. I'm trying to figure out the. . . .
我搞不懂焦距怎样调整
The thing I can't figure out is the zoom-thing.
找到了 好的，等等，站在那里
There it is. Okay, hold on, stay there.
把焦距拉近一点
Got the zoomy-thingy zooming.
待在那里. 我正设法搞懂操作方法 我看看焦距有没有对准
Stay there. I'm trying to figure this out. I wanna see if it focuses.
酷. 非常酷
Cool. Very cool.
真漂亮. 你自己也晓得
So beautiful. If you only knew.
看看你. 天啊，真是个美人
Look at you. God, what a beauty.
有事烦心吗？
Something the matter?
没事. 一点事也没有
Nothing. Nothing at all.
这真的很棒 不，不好. 拿开
- This is really good. - No, it isn't. Go away.
我想我真的对焦了 我找到焦距了. 找到了
I think I'm really zooming. I found the zoom. Found it.
爸
Dad.
该死 妈
- Shit. - Mom.
我睡不着
I can't sleep.
我马上回来. 我马上回来 别睡着了
I'll be back. I'll be back. Don't fall asleep.
有用
It works.
妈，你秀逗了吗？ 你忘了准备我的午餐
Mom, are you nuts? You forgot my lunch.
我没忘. 就在门边 跟我来
I did not. It's by the door. Come with me.
你在嚼什么东西？ 没什么
- What are you chewing? - Nothing.
吐出来，那是什么？
Spit that out. What is that?
真可爱 妈？
- That's lovely. - Mom?
我不想演只笨兔子
I don't want to be a dumb bunny.
甜心，演戏而已 还有其它很多兔子. 会很酷的
Honey, it's a play. There's lots of other bunnies. It'll be cool.
你疯了，妈 那么你告诉我
- You're bonkers, Mom. - So you tell me.
我爱你 我也爱你. 那是什么？
- Love you. - Love you too. What's that?
谢谢
Thank you.
再见
Bye.
嗨，我是保罗・马提尔 哔声后请留下你的讯息. 谢谢
Hi, this is Paul Martel. Leave a message after the beep. Thanks.
喂？ 喂？
Hello? Hello?
- Hello? - Hello?
你在哦
You're there.
我是康妮・桑纳，狂风天碰到的那个人
This is Connie Sumner, the one from the windy day.
哦，那一个
Oh, that one.
膝盖如何？ 你有冰敷吗？
How's the knee? Did you ice it?
有的，我有冰敷且垫高脚 全照你说的去做
Yes, I iced it and I elevated it. You name it, I did it.
好多了 我只是想打个电话跟你道谢
It's much better. I just wanted to call and thank you.
我想问一下你的地址 因为我想要--
I wanted your address because I wanted...
你在哪里？ 你说什么？
- Where are you? - What?
我说，你人在哪里？
I said, where are you?
我在中央车站 真的听不太清楚你的声音
I'm in Grand Central. It's really hard to hear you.
过来看我 什么？
- Come and see me. - What?
对，过来坐一下 我煮咖啡给你喝
Yeah, take a break. I'll make you some coffee.
咖啡？
Coffee?
好的! 好的!
- Okay. - Okay.
再见了
See you. Bye.
靠!
Fuck.
没成了永久残废吧，跳给我看看
No permanent damage, I see.
政府有医疗补助、蓝十字会... 我没投保
- We take Medicaid, Blue Cross. . . . - I'm uninsured.
不行，恐怕我们无法接受慈善救济
No. I'm afraid we don't take charity cases.
开个玩笑啦!
It was a joke.
看看这本. 杰克・伦敦著作
Look at this. Jack London.
"白牙"的初稿，还是原始书套
First edition of White Fang, in the original dust jacket.
我花一元五角买的
And I got it for a buck fifty.
现在值多少呢？ 大概超过4000倍以上价钱
- What's it worth? - About 4000 times more.
是用法文写的 我在学校学过法文
- Those are in French. - I took it in school.
我要脱掉吗？
Do I want to take off something?
你的外套. 要不要把外套脱下来？
Your coat. Would you like to take off your coat?
好的，我的外套
Yes, my coat.
谢谢
Thank you.
但我不能待太久 我还有些事要办
But I can't stay very long. I have some errands I have to run.
我去冲咖啡 好的
- I'll get the coffee. - Okay.
那是点字书 点字
- It's in Braille. - Braille.
不，不，布莱尔 他是法国人
No, no, Braille. He was French.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
什么？ 闭上眼睛
- What? - Close your eyes.
“我母亲为我炖了只鸡
My mother makes me chicken
吃了她的鸡让我咳嗽不已
Her chicken makes me cough
我希望她在炖的时候
I wish that when she made it
能把鸡毛拔干净”
She took the feathers off
书上不是那么写的
It doesn't say that.
(烹饪之乐)
我最好走了 什么？
- I had better go. - Yeah?
我最好走了
I'd better go.
小心，别跌倒了
Take care. Don't fall.
谢谢你的咖啡 你还没喝呢
- Thanks for the coffee. - You didn't drink it.
林赛，嗨 康妮
- Lindsay, hi. - Connie.
我通知他一下 谢谢
- Let me buzz him. - Thanks.
嘿，真是意外. 看看你
Hey, what a surprise. Look at you.
嗨，比尔 嗨，康妮
- Hi, Bill. - Hi, Connie.
我打扰到你们吗？ 不，我正要离开
- Am I interrupting? - No, I'm leaving.
我晚点拿预算案给你 好的，谢谢
- I'll get you the budget later. - All right, thanks.
要喝杯咖啡吗？ 不用了，谢谢
- Would you like a coffee? - No, thank you.
太好了
That's nice.
我不知道你今天要来
I didn't know you were coming in today.
你冷死了 那是什么？
You're freezing. What is that?
我在转角附近，就帮你带了件礼物
I was around the corner and I brought you a present.
哇. 是什么特别日子吗？
Wow. What's the occasion?
没有. 我不知道
Nothing. I don't know.
是中码的，但店员说会越穿越松
It's a medium, but they said it runs large.
看看那个 你不必现在穿上
- Look at that. - You don't have to try it on.
我是老板，我高兴怎样就怎样
I'm the boss. I can do whatever I want.
你觉得怎样？
What do you think?
等我一下
Hold on just a second.
是的？
Yeah?
好的，其它电话暂时不接了
Okay, but hold the other calls.
你在忙，我先走了 坐一下
- You're busy. I'll go. - Sit.
我要走了 不，坐下
- I'll go. - No, sit.
你好，亨利？ 那到底是什么问题停摆了？
Hello, Henry? So, what is this suspension problem?
不，我没收到
No, I never received it.
好，送过来给我
Well, get it to me.
那还不够好 我坐在这里枯等，200台卡车动弹不得
It's not good enough. I'm sitting here with 200 trucks I can't use.
好，安排个时间见面 我要法兰克・博朋在场
Well, set up a meeting. And I want Frank Birnbaum there.
因为我交待别人办事，就得办好才成
Because when I tell someone to do something, I want it done.
我相信你会的
I'm sure you will.
你还得办什么事吗？
So, what else you up to?
拍卖会 是吗？ 你看中了谁？
- Auction. - Yeah? Who'd you hit on?
随便猜猜
The usual suspects.
谁？
Who?
鲍伯・盖洛德 鲍伯？
- Bob Gaylord. - Bob?
叫鲍伯做担保 他们应该派你到中东去
Get Bob to pledge and they should send you to the Middle East.
说吧
So tell me.
什么？
What?
你觉得怎样？ 有像老板吧
What do you think? It's a keeper.
哈 哈
- Hello. - Hello.
我又来了. 我带了些松饼
Here I am again. I brought muffins.
这首是什么音乐？ 你喜欢吗？
- What is this music? - Do you like it?
是的
Yes.
想跳支舞吗？
Do you want to dance?
现在？ 是的
- Now? - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
我必须警告你，由我来带舞 当然，你是美国人
- I have to warn you, I tend to lead. - Of course. You are American.
你以前跳过？ 什么？
- You've done this before. - What?
你交过几个女朋友？
How many girlfriends have you had?
两个
Two.
真的？ 我会骗你吗？
- Really? - Would I lie to you?
不知道. 你会吗？
I don't know. Would you?
你的眼睛真漂亮，你应该连晚上都别闭上
Your eyes are amazing. You should never shut them, not even at night.
你应学会张着眼睛睡觉
You should learn to sleep with your eyes open.
我可以办的到 你能吗？ 〔歌声〕你能能能.....
- I'll work on that. - Will you?
等一下
Hang on.
我想这是错误的
I think this is a mistake.
根本没有错误，全看你愿不愿意而已
There are no mistakes. There's what you do, and what you don't do.
我不能这样
I can't do this.
我忘了外套
Forgot my coat.
不行 怎么？
- I can't. - What?
怎么回事？
What's wrong?
我不知道怎么办 这是不对的
I don't know how to do this. It's wrong.
打我 什么？
- Hit me. - What?
打我
Hit me.
嗨，爱德华 嗨，鲍伯
- Hey, Ed. - Hey, Bob.
好一阵子没看到你了 没错
- Haven't seen you in a while. - No.
这礼拜我一直工作到很晚 真的？ 孩子怎么样？
- I've been working late this week. - Really? How's the boy?
他的生日到了 几岁了？
- It's his birthday. - How old?
9岁
Nine.
那要不要全副武装来个大抢劫？
So any major armed robberies?
不. 不，这礼拜不行
No. No, not this week.
说到这点，多注意一下康妮
Speaking of which, watch out for Connie.
她会叫你在你的抵押单据上签名 什么？
- She'll have you sign over your mortgage. - What?
她有设法说服你捐款吗？ 没有
- Did she try to hit on you for money? - No.
我以为她跟你提过 关于学校拍卖会的事，或者别的
I thought she talked to you about this school auction, or whatever.
没跟我提过
Not me.
我一直出差在外 也许她跟玛吉说过
I've been out of town. Maybe she talked to Maggie.
是的，我想是我搞错了
Yeah, I guess I got it wrong.
总之，我们欠你一顿饭
Anyway, we owe you a dinner.
没错
Yeah.
他不在
He's out.
要不要带东西给你？
Can I get you anything?
不. 不，我很好，谢谢
No. No, I'm fine, thanks.
今天辛苦了？ 不，不太会
- Tough day? - No, not really.
你呢？ 你今天过的如何？
What about you? How was your day?
很好
It was good.
你知道，就平常那些琐事
You know, the usual stuff.
你确定不要点什么吗？
Sure you don't want anything?
不用
No.
康妮？ 什么事？
- Con? - Yeah?
你爱我吗？
Do you love me?
我当然爱你
Of course I love you.
真是个傻问题
What a silly question.
我猜...
I guess. . .
...我是觉得我有点傻
. . .I'm just feeling silly.
我马上上去
I'll be up in a minute.
好的
Okay.
哦，抱歉
Oh, sorry.
你来这里做什么？
What are we doing here?
吃午餐啊!
Having lunch.
我不应该这样 你不应该吃午餐吗？
- I shouldn't be doing this. - You shouldn't have lunch?
不是跟你
Not with you.
我想我们应该离开
I think we should leave.
听着
Listen.
看到那边正要买单的人没？
See those guys over there paying the check?
看到了 好的. 如果是右边的人付钱...
- Yes. - Okay. If the guy on the right pays. . .
...我们马上离开 如果是左边的人付钱的话...
. . .we leave right now. If the guy on the left pays. . .
...我们就留下来
. . .we stay.
而且我要吻你
And I kiss you.
不
No.
账单给我
Give me that.
我赢了
I win.
不 这就是生活
- No. - C'est la vie.
别那样. 不要
Don't do it. Don't.
双人房？ 当然
- Room for two? - Of course.
音乐很好听. 是什么音乐？
Nice music. What is it?
是...
It's. . .
...我想是非洲音乐吧
. . .African, I think.
我喜欢
I like it.
拿去
Here.
我们回房吧
Let's go to bed.
快点 在这里陪我
- Come on. - Stay here with me.
我好冷 留下来
- I'm cold. - Stay.
留在这里陪我 我好冷
- Stay here with me. - I'm cold.
我们走
Let's go.
中午一块用餐如何？
How about lunch today?
你有空吗？
You free?
我有一大堆募捐者的物品 得挑出要拍卖的
I have all this fundraiser stuff. Auction things to pick up.
要是你方便的话，我们可以提早一点 中午12点怎么样？
We can do an early one if you want. How about 12:00?
12点？
12:00?
是的
Yeah.
12点时不晓得会不会饿？
Will I be hungry at 12:00?
我们可以一块进去用餐
We could go in together.
我会等你
I'll wait for you.
我还要一个钟头才有空 没关系，我等你
- I won't be ready for another hour. - That's all right. I'll wait.
哦，该死 怎么了？
- Oh, shit. - What?
我刚刚想起...
I just remembered. . .
我今天12点半要到乔琪安娜店里做美容
. . .I have a facial at 12:30 at Georgianna's today.
哦，好的
Oh, well.
你得保持漂亮点，好吗？
You gotta stay beautiful, right?
乔琪安娜美容院，是吧？
Georgianna's, huh?
浪费钱
Waste of money.
对，在曼哈顿
Yeah, Manhattan.
美容院称作乔琪娜
A beauty salon called Georgina.
哦，是的，没错. 是的，乔琪安娜 没错
Oh, yeah, right. Yes, Georgianna's. That's right.
谢谢
Thank you.
你好，我想确认一下今天12点半的预约
Hello, I'm calling to confirm an appointment today at 12:30.
桑纳. 康妮・桑纳
Sumner. Connie Sumner.
S-U-M-N-E-R.
她会不会是改了预约时间？
Could she be down for another time?
不客气，谢谢
No, thank you.
康妮？ 是康妮
Connie? It's Connie.
康妮？
Connie?
特蕾西？
Tracy?
嗨. 我正想打电话给你 电话老是...
- Hi. I was gonna call you. - They all say that. . .
...我打电话谈兔子装的事 见过家庭计划中心的莎莉
. . .when I call about bunny costumes. You know Sally from Planned Parenthood.
嗨，好久不见 好久了
- Hi. It's been a while. - Too long.
你保养的真好 你要去哪？
- You look amazing. - So where you headed?
我正要去挑些厨房用的窗帘
I was going to look for some window shades for the kitchen.
我们要去喝咖啡 你何不跟我们一块去？
We're gonna go and have coffee. Why don't you join us?
哦，我快迟到了 买窗帘会迟到？
- Oh, I'm gonna be late. - For window shades?
少来了 好吧
- Come on. - Okay.
嗨，你好吗？
Hi, how are you?
我要去打个电话
I'm just gonna make a phone call.
好的 拿我的手机去打
- Sure. - Let me get that for you.
她可以用我手机打就好了呀 你说的对
- She could've used my cell phone. - Oh, you're right.
嗨，是我
Hi, it's me.
说起来你可能不信 我人在转角的咖啡厅
You won't believe this. I'm at that cafe around the corner.
你干嘛介绍我是家庭计划中心的莎莉？
Why do you introduce me as Sally from Planned Parenthood?
听起来好像我在推销保险套似的
It makes it sound like I'm handing out condoms.
我被困在这里了
I'm stuck here.
等我好吗？
Will you wait for me?
等我!
Wait for me.
我打电话提醒葛萝莉亚 去拿送洗的衣服
I called Gloria to remind her to pick up the dry cleaning.
查理真是人见人爱
Charlie is so adorable.
谢谢
Thank you.
我吃不下
I can't eat.
我要一杯咖啡 我想我也来杯咖啡好了
- I'll have a coffee. - Well, I guess I'll have coffee too.
再失陪一下，我上个洗手间
Excuse me again. Ladies' room.
天啊，她看起来气色真好
God, she looks good.
你想她有去做整容吗？ 她何必整容？ 她还耀眼的很
- You think she's had work? - Why would she? She's still gorgeous.
趁现在早点做，免得到时成了黄脸婆
They do it early now before it goes to shit.
我朋友在外面
I have friends out there.
你带我来这最棒的地方
You take me to the best places.
我来
Let me.
她不像你说的那样. 她真的很漂亮 当然漂亮了
- She's not like that. She's really nice. - Of course she is.
所以才更糟糕 她既漂亮又温柔
That makes it worse. She's nice and she's sweet.
她的臀部跟在大学时一样玲珑有致
And her ass is in exactly the same place it was in college.
你有在打网球吗？
Are you taking tennis?
哦，我可不会称那回事为"打网球"
Oh, I wouldn't call what I do "taking tennis. "
你回来了. 我正开始要担心你呢 不，我很好
- There you are. I was starting to worry. - No, I'm fine.
我们还以为你被帅哥给绑架了呢
We thought that heartthrob abducted you.
什么帅哥啊？
What heartthrob?
你没看到柜台那个男的吗？ 好帅哦
You didn't see him at the counter? He was gorgeous.
我没听懂 你的扣子没扣好
- I miss everything. - Your button's undone.
哦，谢谢
Oh. Thank you.
就是他
That's him.
我看他对我有意思
I can see the appeal.
如果他看我两次 我马上转头过去
If he looked at me twice, I'd be on my back.
你不会的 我会的. 为何说不会？
- You would not. - I would so. Why not?
两项理由: 亚当和你的孩子
A couple of reasons: Adam and your kids.
你知道，特蕾西，不必给他们知道
You know, Trace, they wouldn't have to know.
这很可能是我自己跨越禁忌尺度
It could be something I did for myself, to broaden my horizons.
就像上陶艺班一样
Like taking a pottery class.
恋爱又不像上陶艺班 有可能
- An affair isn't like taking pottery. - Could be.
恋情会像那样开始发展出来 然后就发生了关系...
It would start out like that. Then something would happen. . .
被人发现有了外遇 最后结局都很惨
. . .someone finds out or someone falls in love and it ends disastrously.
总是以悲剧收场
They always end disastrously.
不
No.
什么时候？
When?
很久以前了
It was a long time ago.
如果可能的话，我希望能重来一遍
And it's the one thing in my life I would undo if I could.
你越过街道就只是为了干我？
Did you just fuck me across the street?
是的
I did.
我们可以立刻结束这段关系 谁也不会受到伤害
We could end this now and no one would get hurt.
是的. 我想如果现在结束的话 我会受到伤害
Yeah. I think if we ended this now, I'd get hurt.
所以不管怎样，有人会受到伤害？ 也许不会
- So no matter what, someone gets hurt? - Maybe not.
也许我们会彼此厌倦对方
Maybe we'll get tired of each other.
天啊，真希望我能厌倦你
God, I hope I get tired of you.
你深植我心坎底
You're in my mind.
每早醒来第一个想到的就是你
You're the only thing in my mind when I wake up every morning.
还没张眼之前，你就浮现在我脑海了
You're in my brain before I even open my eyes.
你想的是什么？ 不一定
- What do you think of? - That depends.
如果哪一天不知能否见到你时 我会很紧张...
If it's a day when I don't know if I'm gonna get to see you, I'm anxious. . .
...想尽借口来这里看你
. . .thinking of excuses to come to the city to see you.
你知道我们要见面的日子吗？
And the days you know we'll meet?
每逢那些日子...
On those days. . .
...我...
. . .I'm. . .
平静多了，也痛恨我自己
. . .calm and hating myself.
这里只有这个
This is what we have over here.
我下午就帮你准备好了
I'll have it ready for you this afternoon.
爱德华，怎么了？ 听起来很重要的样子
Ed, what's up? Sounded important.
我听说你跟邓巴、布尔克 及其它公司洽谈
I've heard you're talking with Dunbar and Brinks and other companies.
你从哪里听来的？
Where did you hear that?
嗯，听着
Well, look.
我想他们可能是要挖角我过去 若你的意思是那样
I suppose they could be wooing me, if that's what you mean.
很明显地一堆人要挖你跳槽 还是谁在挖谁呢？
Apparently a lot of people are wooing you. Or who's wooing who?
你在说什么呀？ 我跟一些人谈过了
What are you talking about? So I talked to some people.
那又怎样？ 这是关于忠诚，比尔
- So what? - This is about loyalty, Bill.
我让你走 要是有需要的话我可以写推荐函
I'm letting you go. You'll have my recommendation if you need it.
我有一家人要养活，爱德华
I have a family, Ed.
你这里也有一家人
You had a family here.
不，等一等 你跟我谈论家人？
No, wait a minute. You're telling me about family?
最重要的事你都被蒙在鼓里
You don't know the first goddamn thing about it.
注意你自己该死的家人，爱德华
Look at your own fucking family, Ed.
他妈的注意一下!
Take a goddamn look at that.
爱德华 法兰克
- Ed. - Frank.
谢谢你这么快赶来
Thanks for coming on such short notice.
这是私事，与公事无关
This is personal, it's not business.
考虑一下 你可能不愿意牵扯到这件事
Think about it. You might not want to get involved.
但我需要找个信得过的人
But I need someone I can trust.
我要你跟踪一个人
I want you to follow somebody.
我要你跟踪我老婆
I want you to follow my wife.
着火了，妈 什么？
- It's burning, Mom. - What?
着火了. 鸡肉
It's burning. The chicken.
可恶
Shit.
水滚了，妈. 水滚开了!
It's boiling, Mom. It's boiling!
谢谢
Thank you.
小心! 小心!...
Watch it. Watch it.
抱歉，鸡肉有点烧焦
Chicken's a little dry. I'm sorry.
没关系
It's fine.
我明天要去芝加哥
I have to go to Chicago tomorrow.
去多久？ 不会很久. 可能只住一个晚上
- For how long? - Not long. Probably just a night.
几点的班机？
What time's your flight?
八点
Eight o'clock.
早上？
A.M.?
戴安・德莱厄尔的儿子跟艾美・琳恩的女儿 要结婚
Dianne Dreyer's son is marrying Amy Lynn's daughter.
我绝不要结婚 为什么不要？
- I'm never getting married. - Why not?
我讨厌女孩子
I hate girls.
你以后就会改变心意的
You might change your mind. That happens sometimes.
我才不会
I won't.
什么？ 我今天将比尔・史东解雇了
- What? - I fired Bill Stone today.
你是在烦那件事吗？ 我没在烦
- That's what's bothering you? - Nothing's bothering me.
你为什么要解雇他？
Why did you fire him?
他不够负责 什么是负责？
- He's not accountable. - What's accountable?
是不是像人吃人？ 不是
- Isn't it like people who eat people? - No.
那是食人族，甜心
That's a cannibal, honey.
总之，我再也信不过他了
Anyway, I can't trust him anymore.
所以如果你碰到桃莉，你就会明白
So if you run into Dolly, you'll know.
怎么？ 没想到你这样!
- What? - I can't believe you!
我做了什么？
What did I do?
糟糕!
Shit!
快点!
Come on!
真对不起. 真的很对不起
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
甜心，你没事吧？
Honey, you okay?
你一定非常担心 住手，妈. 别人会看到
- You must have been so worried. - Stop, Mom. People can see.
嗨，我是保罗・马提尔 哔声后请留下您的讯息
Hi, this is Paul Martel. Leave a message after the beep.
妈？
Mom?
你应该上床睡觉了
You're supposed to be in bed.
你在哭，妈 哦，甜心
- You're crying, Mom. - Oh, honey.
妈咪只是有点难过而已 来吧，我带你回房睡觉
Mommy's just a little sad, that's all. Come on, I'll take you bed.
我带你去睡觉
Let's get you into bed.
别难过了，妈 爸明天就回家了
Don't be sad, Mom. Dad will be home tomorrow.
他叫保罗・马提尔
His name is Paul Martel.
住在梅瑟街433号，3号公寓
He lives at 433 Mercer Street, Apartment 3.
她白天时候去找他
She sees him during the day.
通常都在午餐时间前后
Usually goes around lunchtime.
约逗留个两、三小时
Stays about two hours, maybe three.
他们去电影院？
They go to the movies?
那天有去 除此之外，还去了他家
They did that day. Otherwise, they're in his place.
快点接!
Pick up.
嘿，小姐!
Hey, lady!
你钥匙忘了给
Forgot your keys.
等等!
Wait!
她是谁？ 她是谁？
Who is she? Who is she?
冷静点! 你在干什么？
Calm down! What are you doing?
还有几个？ 5个、10个？
How many are there? Five, ten?
我算什么，星期一那一个？ 我弄错日子了吗？
What am I, the Monday one? Did I get my day wrong?
她只是个朋友，好吗？ 只是朋友
She's just a friend, okay? Just a friend.
你这该死的骗子 我？ 我是骗子？
- You're a fucking liar. - Me? I'm the liar?
我不会再跟你来往了
I can't do this anymore.
那好. 回去你的郊区和车库 打你的网球--
Fine. Go back to your suburb and car pool, your tennis...
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
操你 会教你很爽的
- Fuck you. - That'll make you happy.
去你的
Fuck you.
不，不行
No, I can't.
保罗，结束了
Paul, it's over.
不行
I can't.
我恨你. 我恨你 我知道
- I hate you. I hate you. - I know.
住手，我不行
Stop it, I can't.
你要干我吗？ 你要我干吗？
- Are you gonna fuck me? - You want me to?
我要 说出来
- I want you to. - Say it.
我要你干我 说出来
- I want you to fuck me. - Say it.
我要你干我
I want you to fuck me.
谢谢. 非常谢谢你
Thank you. Thank you very much.
真的很谢谢你
Thank you very much, indeed.
什么事？
Yes?
你是保罗・马提尔？ 是的
- You're Paul Martel? - Yes.
你多大年纪？
How old are you?
你是谁？
Who are you?
爱德华・桑纳
Edward Sumner.
康妮的丈夫
Connie's husband.
我可以...？
May I. . .?
我可以进去吗？
May I come in?
当然可以
Yeah. Sure.
你想喝点什么吗？ 好的
- Would you like a drink? - Yeah, why not?
我有威士忌、伏特加、柳橙汁....
I have Scotch, vodka, orange juice. . . .
伏特加
Vodka.
冰的吗？
Is it cold?
是的
Yeah.
我放在冰箱里头
I keep it in the freezer.
我家里也是
So do I, at home.
那么告诉我，你是怎么...
So tell me, how did you. . .
...认识我老婆的？
. . .meet my wife?
意外
By accident.
在街上. 那时刮大风，她的膝盖受伤....
On the street. There was a windstorm, she hurt her knee and. . . .
你就是他
You're him.
她跟你说的？
She told you about that?
对
Yes.
你还好吧？
How's it going?
很好，很好. 我是指我没事
Fine. Fine. I mean, okay.
你们在此幽会？ 是的
- This is where you meet? - Yes.
她喜欢吗？ 我猜是的. 她没抱怨过
- She likes it? - I guess. She never complained.
你们都一直待在这里，或者也照样外出？
Do you stay in all the time, or do you go out too?
看情况. 有时候会出门
It depends. Sometimes we go out.
那她喜欢出门吗？
And she likes that?
她喜欢这附近？
She likes this neighborhood?
我想比住在郊区还刺激
More exciting than the suburbs, I guess.
你知道我们已经结婚11年了吗？
Do you know we have been married 11 years?
我们有个儿子
We have a son.
她告诉过我
She told me.
还要吗？
More?
好的，谢谢
Yes, please.
他就是我们搬离这城市的原因
He's the reason that we left the city.
康妮认为对他比较好
Connie thought it'd be better for him.
她说是你的主意
She told me it was your idea.
你们...谈论我？
You talk about me?
好多书
A lot of books.
作些买卖
A lot of buying and selling.
我不知道能那样
I didn't know it did that.
你怎么有这个？ 是个礼物
- Where did you get this? - It was a gift.
她送的？
From her.
她为什么要送你？ 不知道
- Why would she do that? - I don't know.
也许她只是想买点东西送我
Maybe she just wanted to buy me something.
这不是她买给你的 是我送她的
She didn't buy this for you. I gave it to her.
我受不了 怎么了？
- I can't do this. - What?
我受不了. 我受不了
I can't do this. I can't do this.
我觉得不舒服. 我不行--
I'm feeling sick. I can't...
要喝点水吗？
You want some water?
我觉得不舒服. 我--
I'm feeling sick. I'm...
我觉得--
I feel...
不舒服. 我觉得不舒服
I'm not well. I'm not feeling well.
我不是--
I'm not...
我觉得不--
I'm not feeling...
天啊!
God!
你不能死
You can't die.
嗨，我是保罗・马提尔 哔声后请留下您的讯息
Hi, this is Paul Martel. Leave a message after the beep.
嗨，是我
Hi, it's me.
听着
Listen.
这件事我不想对着录音机说...
I don't like saying this to your machine...
...但我必须结束这段关系
...but I have to end this.
只是我...我不能再这样下去了
I just... I can't do it anymore.
我不能这样子生活下去
I can't live like this.
我厌倦了欺骗及伤害我的家人
I'm so tired of lying and hurting my family.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我希望....
And I hope...
我不知道我希望怎样
I don't know what I hope.
对不起
I'm sorry.
讯息已删除
Messages erased.
紧张吗？
Does that pinch?
不会
No.
你知道你独唱的部份吗？ 知道
- Do you know your solo? - Yep.
我可以听吧？
Can I hear it?
需要帮忙吗？ 不用，我很好
- Need a hand? - No, I'm fine.
谢了
Thanks.
你去哪了？
Where were you?
没事吧？
You okay?
你知道你很出色吗？
You were spectacular, you know that?
他是不是很棒？ 是很棒
- Wasn't he great? - Great.
他太棒了，很棒
He was great. Great.
真的很棒
Really great.
我得帮忙打扫 回家后再给晚安吻，好吗？
I have to help clean up. I'll kiss you good night when I get home, okay?
抱歉，爱德华. 好像是我把你绑死了 没关系
- Sorry, Ed. Looks like I nailed you. - It's all right.
没关系，杰瑞
It's all right, Jerry.
你最好检查看看这打不打的开
You better check to see if this will open.
没什么. 车子很好
It's nothing. This is fine.
车有撞凹吗，爸？ 是的
- Did he dent you, Dad? - Yes, he did. Yes.
要叫警察来吗，爸？
Can we call the cops, Dad?
我们检查一下后车厢 我们明天再谈
- Let's check the trunk. - We'll talk tomorrow.
一下子就好了 不!
- It'll just take a second. - No!
哦，我的妈呀
Oh, my God.
查理，瞧瞧你爸，告诉他哪里不对劲
Charlie, look at your dad and tell me what's wrong.
怎么了？
What?
他的鞋子! 两只鞋子颜色不一样
His shoes. They're different colors.
甜心，你看来糟透了
Honey, you look awful.
昨晚怎么回事？ 你有睡吗？ 我起床后找不到你
What happened last night? Did you sleep? I got up and looked for you.
我只是...
I just. . .
...去透个气
. . .got some air.
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
很好
Yeah.
搬到这里你喜欢吗？
Do you like it here?
什么？ 我当然喜欢这里
What? Of course I like it here.
我们不一定得住在这里 我们可以搬回城市住
We don't have to stay here. We can move back to the city.
甜心，你有何心事？
Honey, what has gotten into you?
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
是的，没事. 我很好
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine. Fine.
你还好吧？ 我很好
- Are you okay? - I'm fine.
大家都很好 我们哪里也别搬
Everybody's fine. And we're not moving anywhere.
警察来了，妈
The cops are here, Mom.
他们来干什么？ 应该没什么
- What do they want? - I'm sure it's nothing.
纽约警探，妈
N.Y.P.D., Mom.
桑纳太太？ 我是狄恩警探 这位是米罗尼克警探，纽约警探
Mrs. Sumner? I'm Detective Dean, this is Detective Mirojnick, N.Y.P.D.
有什么事吗？ 怎么了？
Something happen? Is something wrong?
你认识保罗・马提尔吗？
Do you know a Paul Martel?
是的，不太熟. 怎么？ 你知道他在哪吗？
- Yes, not very well. Why? - Do you know where he is?
不知道
No.
我想在家吧
At home, I would imagine.
你知道他住哪吗？
Do you know where he lives?
苏活区，是不是？
SoHo, isn't it?
在他桌上找到你的名字和电话号码
Your name and number were found on his desk.
他做了什么坏事吗？ 不清楚
- Has he done something wrong? - We don't know.
他的家人报案说他失踪了
He's been reported missing by his family.
他老婆不知道他现在人在哪里
His wife doesn't know where he is.
我不知道他结过婚了
I didn't know he was married.
分居了
Separated.
你上回见到他是什么时候？
When did you see him last?
不记得了，很难说
I don't know, it's hard to say.
他是个书商
He's a book dealer.
不太认识 我之前要跟他买书
I barely know him. I was going to buy books from him.
买了吗？ 不，还没
- And did you? - No, not yet.
发生什么事了吗？ 你认为他没事吧？
Has something happened? You think he's all right?
一时还很难说
It's hard to say at this point.
我们正在调查
We're working on it.
总之，谢谢. 谢谢你抽空回答 谢谢
- Anyway, thanks. Thanks for your time. - Thank you.
我喜欢这种玻璃雪花的玩意 我儿子就有一些
I like these snow-glass things. My boy has some of these.
如果有他消息的话，麻烦通知我们 没问题
- If you hear from him, let us know. - Certainly.
爸! 警察今天来我们家
Dad! Cops came to our house today.
警察？ 他们来做什么？
Cops? What did they want?
有人失踪了
Someone's missing.
他们必须询问每个人，你知道的
And they have to check everyone, you know.
谁失踪了？
Who was it?
甜心，坐好
Honey, sit up straight.
谁失踪了？ 我想你不认识他
- Who was it? - I don't think you know him.
是个卖书的
He sells books.
我忘了在哪见过他
I forget where I met him.
他是个坏蛋吗，妈？
Was it a bad guy, Mom?
警察为什么要给你问话？
Why did they want to talk to you?
我猜他有我的名字和电话号码
I guess he had my name and number.
他为何会有你的电话号码？
Why would he have your number?
我想是跟他买过书的关系
I think I bought a book from him.
小心点. 慢慢来 嘿，查理!
- Be careful. Take it easy. - Hey, Charlie!
哦，亲爱的 哦，我希望你住近一点
Oh, my darling. Oh, I wished you lived closer.
主啊，感谢您赐给我们食物 以及您的恩宠
Lord, bless this food to our use, and us to thy service.
提醒我们去帮助别人，阿门
And help us be ever mindful of the needs of others. Amen.
阿门
Amen.
很好，爱德华
Very nice, Edward.
好了!
All right!
我说个你们不知道的爱德华的事 靠过来一点
I have a story you don't know about Edward. Gather close.
你好，桑纳太太
Hello, Mrs. Sumner.
很抱歉周末还来打扰你们 我是狄恩警探
Sorry to bother you on the weekend. I'm Detective Dean.
这位是米罗尼克警探，纽约警探 好的
- This is Detective Mirojnick, N.Y.P.D. - Okay.
我们希望能跟你谈个几分钟
We were hoping to talk to you for a few minutes.
没问题
Sure.
查理，我们上去走廊那边一下 我可以过去吗？
- Charlie, we're going up on the porch. - Can I come?
不行，甜心. 待在外面 跟波比玩一下，我们马上回来
No, sweetheart. Stay out here. Play with Poppy, we'll be right back.
不知道您老婆有没有提过 上星期我们有来过
I don't know if your wife mentioned, we were here a week ago.
调查保罗・马提尔的事
About Paul Martel.
有的，失踪了的人
Yeah, the man who was missing.
嗯，他不会再失踪了 尸体上周末被人发现了
Well, he's not missing anymore. His body was discovered last weekend.
天啊，太可怕了
God, that's terrible.
哦，我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你想起来在哪见到马提尔先生了吗 桑纳太太？
Do you recall where you met Mr. Martel, Mrs. Sumner?
我说过了 不，夫人，你没说过
- I told you. - No, ma'am, you didn't.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我想不起来
I can't remember.
我想大概是募捐者吧
A fundraiser, I think.
你能说的更详细点吗？
Can you be more specific?
茱利亚德
Juilliard.
茱利亚德？
Juilliard?
音乐学校
The music school.
是的，我知道茱利亚德是什么 你当然知道. 抱歉
- Yes, I know what Juilliard is. - Of course you do. I'm sorry.
你也去过吗，先生？
Were you there too, sir?
是的. 是的，我想我去过
Yes. Yes, I think I was.
嗯，也许你见过马提尔先生
Well, maybe you met Mr. Martel.
不. 不，就我记得没见过
No. No, not that I remember.
也许你会认得他
Maybe you'd recognize him.
不，我从没见过他
No, I've never met him before.
是他吗？ 是的. 是的
- Is that him? - Yes. Yes.
你曾到过他的公寓？
You ever been to his apartment?
没有
No.
没有，我几乎不认识他
No, I hardly knew him.
我不知道他为何会有我的电话号码 也许他喜欢你
- I didn't know why he had my number. - Maybe he liked you.
听着，够了
Look, that's enough.
所以你从未到过他的公寓 那附近地区呢？
So you've never been to his apartment. How about the neighborhood?
逛过那里吗？ 没有
- Hang out down there? - No.
不，不常...
No, not often. . .
...还是不，从来没有
. . .or no, never.
从来没有 我不记得上回到苏活区是什么时候了
Never. I can't remember the last time I was in SoHo.
事实上是四个星期前
It was four weeks ago, actually.
你有一张马提尔公寓前的停车券 上面日期是四星期前
You got a parking ticket in front of Martel's apartment, four weeks ago.
哦，那个. 对，我跟朋友在一间小店喝咖啡
Oh, that. Right. I had coffee with friends at a little place.
我忘了
I forgot.
是特蕾西和莎莉 哦，是的. 是的. 对
- It was Tracy and Sally. - Oh, yeah. Yes. Yep.
听好...
Look. . .
我老婆知道的全告诉你了，我也是
. . .my wife has told you everything she knows, so have I.
不介意的话，我去找我儿子
If you don't mind, we'd like to get back to our son.
好啦
All right.
我怎么忘了给你我的名片呢？ 我有你的名片
- Why don't I give you my card? - I have your card.
对啊
Right.
祝你们周末愉快 你们也是
- Enjoy your weekend. - You too.
桑纳，拜托
Sumner, please.
哦，天啊
Oh, my God.
康妮？
Connie?
嗨，特蕾西
Hi, Tracy.
我只是来拿我今晚要穿的丝质套装
I'm just picking up my silk suit for tonight.
我想穿这件黑色的
I was thinking of wearing the black.
我捐给了古德威 换别人好好亮相一番
I'm giving it to Goodwill. Let someone else be gorgeous for a change.
估且不谈我们明亮的个性 我们该带什么过去？
What should we bring, aside from our sparkling personalities?
我们准备得如何了？ 很好
- How we doing? - Fine.
要帮手吗？ 不用
- Need help? - No.
白酒不冰了 所以我把它放到进冰箱里
Well, the white is not cold, so I'm gonna put it in the freezer.
记得提醒我放在里面，好吗？
Just remind me it's in there, all right?
大部份的人喜欢喝红酒
Most people drink red anyway.
我喜欢这些小玩意 还有什么地方你们没去过？
I love these things. Is there any place you guys haven't been?
罗森索家有795个呢
The Rosenthals got 795 for their place.
短短两天就接获六张订单 他们正在从事招标
- In two days they had six offers. - Sealed bids is how they do it now.
你觉得这间房子值多少，爱德华？
What do you think this place is worth, Ed?
不清楚. 如果卖了房子，要搬去哪？
I don't know. If you sell your house, where do you go?
以那些价钱，大溪地 曼谷
- At those prices, Tahiti. - Bangkok.
康妮，这个是哪来的？
Connie, where is this one from?
斐济
Fiji.
记住，杰夫 我要你带我去斐济
Remember, Jeff, I asked you to take me to Fiji.
然后再带我去夏威夷 每天悠闲地钓钓鱼....
And then you took me to Hawaii. We went fishing every single. . . .
怎么了，爱德华？
What happened, Edward?
你干了什么事？
What did you do?
是你伤害他的吗？
Did you hurt him?
爱德华？
Edward?
是你伤害他的吗？
Did you hurt him?
你做的，是不是？
You did, didn't you?
天啊，爱德华
Jesus, Edward.
说话呀
Talk to me.
告诉我你做了什么!
Tell me what you did!
不，你告诉我你做了什么
No, you tell me what you did.
你是如何一而再三地和他上床 还敢骗我!
How you fucked him, over and over and over. You lied to me!
三番两次地 爱德华，拜托--
- Over and over and over. - Edward, please...
不，你不用马上回答
No, you don't talk to me now.
我尽心尽力地付出...
I gave everything. . .
...为了这个家
. . .for this family.
费尽心血
Everything.
你又做了什么？
And what did you do?
你像是毫无要紧地将它丢弃一旁
You threw it all away, like it was nothing.
为什么？
For what?
为了那个该死的小孩
To the fucking kid.
你以为我不知道？
You didn't think I'd know?
我没感觉到吗？ 从第一天起我就晓得了
I wouldn't feel it? I knew it from the very first day.
因为我太了解你了，康妮 我了解你却也该死的恨你
Because I know you, Connie. I know you and I fucking hate you.
我并不想杀他，我想杀的是你!
I didn't want to kill him, I wanted to kill you!
哦，天啊
Oh, my God.
爱德华. 哦，天啊
Edward. Oh, my God.
天啊
Oh, my God.
妈，看我做的
Mom, look what I did.
甜心，不要紧. 不要紧的
Honey, it's okay. That's okay.
对不起，妈
I'm sorry, Mom.
只是意外，谁都难免有意外
It's an accident. Everybody has accidents.
你怎不回房睡，妈？
Why aren't you in bed, Mom?
我不知道
I don't know.
查理，看着我
Charlie, look at me.
我要你明白...
I want you to know. . .
...我爱你远胜于世上任何一切
. . .that I love you, more than anything in the world.
我要你知道你爸和我两个...
And I want you to know that your daddy and me both. . .
...会永远永远爱你
. . .will always, always love you.
无论如何
No matter what.
好吗？ 好的
- Okay? - Okay.
好了，甜心
Come on, sweetie.
我们把你的床整理的干干净净，好吗？
Let's go fix up your bed all nice and fresh, okay?
好的
All right.
你可以上来清洗一下伤口
You can come on up and clean it off, no?
来吧! 我不是什么连环杀手，我发誓
Come on. I'm not an ax murderer. I promise.
出租车!
Taxi.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们要怎么办？
What are we going to do?
我好害怕
I'm so scared.
我去自首
I'll turn myself in.
不
No.
不，我们会大步揽过的
No, we can get through this.
我们一天一次，每次搬一点点
We'll take it one day at a time.
神不知鬼不觉的
No one will know.
而我们知道啊
We'll know.
3200，3500，3800，4000...
3200, 3500, 3800, 4000. . .
...42，45，4800!
. . .42, 45, 4800!
我们可以逃的无影无踪
We can disappear.
可以筹一点钱
We can raise some money.
全都卖掉，然后离开这个国家
Sell everything and just leave the country.
小姐？
Senorita?
墨西哥
Mexico.
有何不可？
Why not?
我们可以买间靠海边的小房子
We can get a little house on the beach.
用别的化名
Take a different name.
大家都是这样子做
People do it all the time.
我们要怎么告诉查理？
What will we tell Charlie?
告诉他这是一次冒险
Tell him it's an adventure.
我们可以整天钓鱼
We could fish all day.
学学如何弹吉它
We could learn to play the guitar.
每晚对你唱小夜曲好让你入睡
I would serenade you to sleep every night.
就在海边度过余生
We'll just live the rest of our lives on that beach.
等我们死了，就葬在海里
And then when we die, we can just push out to sea.
你认为怎样？
What do you think?
听起来蛮不错的
Sounds perfect.